Isreal Onaopemipo Aluko

29, Ire akari street, Okoila, Ijoko, Ogun State, Nigeria.

- linkedin.com/in/eazyisreal/ eazyisreal192@gmail.com
- github.com/eazyisreal/ +234 90 2451 0594 https://eazyisreal.netlify.app/

Education

Olusegun Agagu University of Science and Technology Bachelor of technology, Applied Geophysics.

Ondo State, Nigeria January, 2016 - November, 2021

About

Web developer with proficiency in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript as well as a number of frameworks and libraries. I have a strong aptitude for creating front-end web applications that prioritize user delight and experience. I have a strong work ethic and prefer tasks that call for both analytical and inventive thinking. My desire to learn motivates me to continuously look for new information and resources that can improve my productivity and skills. I have knowledge of front-end development as well as back-end development using the Django framework. I have the ability to create dependable, scalable, and effective web apps. My understanding of both front-end and back-end development enables me to approach web development holistically.

Experience

Edvent digital studio

Abuja, Nigeria

Web Developer (Internship)

August 2022 - November 2022

- Developed unique modules for a website theme on Hubspot using React.js and HubL templating engine.
- Created an authentication system with social Oauth using Laravel PHP
- Worked collaboratively with the team to ensure that software was secure, user-friendly and fully functional.
- Gained valuable experience in web development and further developed skills in React.js

Voluntary Service

Social Media Manager, Premir_Medimart, October 2022 – present:

Manage social media accounts, create and curate content, and engage with the online community to increase visibility

Social Media Manager/Community manager, Aricah, December 2022 – present:

Manage online forums and groups, monitor engagements and provide technical support to members to ensure a positive and productive online community

Professional Development

Jobberman softskill training

September, 2022

 Learned the effective communication, Leadership and management, Emotional Intelligence and Time management skills.

Web development, Progate

August, 2022

Learned the methods and ways of integrating bootstrap, JQuery and Saas into web development to enable the
design of faster and more responsive websites. Learned the basics of React, Node.js, SQL and Command
Line.

Fullstack web development, I4GXZURI

May, 2022

Learned the basics of web development. Built a Fullstack web application alongside team mates.

Additional Information

Skills:

- Technical skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python 3, Tailwind CSS, Sass, Django, Linux, Database Management.
- Soft skills: Effective Communication, Teamwork and collaboration, Problem-solving, Adaptability and flexibility, Time management and organization, Active listening, Empathy and emotional intelligence, Creativity and innovations.
- Document Formation Skills: Microsoft Suite, Google Workspace, Notion.

Activities: Google developers' group, Drumming,

Languages: English (Professional working proficiency), Spanish (Beginner), Yoruba (Native, fluent).